And also Bazinga.com
was taken.
(Barry:)Anyway, thanks again.
(Barry:)Cooper, suck eggs.
(Sheldon:)Since when do you help out
Barry Kripke?
(Amy:)Well, I'd been thinking about
a cellular automata approach
(Amy:)to neuronal connectivity,
(Amy:)and I thought it might have
some interesting applications
(Amy:)to string theory--
it's not a big deal.
(Sheldon:)Oh, really?
(Sheldon:)When I was doing string theory
and hit a dead end,
(Sheldon:)why didn't you try to help me?
(Amy:)I did-- you said the only
math biologists know is
(Amy:)if you have three frogs
and one hops away,
(Amy:)that leaves two frogs.
(Sheldon:)That's pretty funny,
that does sound like me.
(Sheldon:)But that doesn't mean
(Sheldon:)that you should be
standing on street corners
(Sheldon:)handing out your math
to whatever guy comes along.
(Amy:)Sheldon, we're all scientists.
(Amy:)I helped out
a fellow colleague.
(Amy:)You're being petty.
(Sheldon:)I'm being petty?
(Sheldon:)You know Barry and I
have a professional rivalry.
(Sheldon:)You heard him--
he told me to suck eggs.
(Sheldon:)If we were friends,
he would have suggested
(Sheldon:)I suck something
more pleasant.
(Sheldon:)Why are you laughing?
(Sheldon:)Did you learn
something?